<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</title>
    <link>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 10:43:29 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Joining Icalia Labs</title>
      <link>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/joining-icalia-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 10:43:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/joining-icalia-labs/</guid>
      <description>I had a wild 2017, not exactly in a good way. Many sad events happened to my family in that year, thankfully our newborn helped us a lot. It gave us those moments of joy we needed.
During many months I lost focus in my training and work, but I needed to get back on my feet. So I started a new business inspired by the trend of productizing your services, aimed to create websites for small companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inherit fortune</title>
      <link>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/inherit-fortune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 10:33:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/inherit-fortune/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago my father stayed in the hospital around 3 weeks, as in most places in the world, healthcare is very expensive, so he has social insurance which gives you medical care but it comes with a price. Hospitals are packed, few places to sit, little information and I don’t even want to talk about the restrooms.
You’ll see the mid to low income population in those places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play with fire and you get burned</title>
      <link>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/play-with-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 09:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/play-with-fire/</guid>
      <description>On July 23, 2017, I experienced the worst accident I have ever had in my life.
It was a long-awaited weekend, where we went to Cuatrocienegas to have a great time with the family. Everything was excellent and wonderful, we finished going to the main places, the only place that was left before returning home was the marble mine, being there and having seen all I just had this urge to climb the highest stone (8-10 meters approx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resuming</title>
      <link>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/resuming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 08:20:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://v3.ramiroruiz.com/blog/resuming/</guid>
      <description>On my birthday 5 years and 6 months ago on September 9, 2012, I wrote this:
 Hi there, well after so many years being part of the web passive community, today in my birthday I finally decided to make the change and start sharing the little I know and the many questions I ask myself constantly. Maybe I’m starting a bit late but I think I&amp;rsquo;ll take positive things from this instead of not doing it, besides I&amp;rsquo;m a little tired of being one more behind the monitor, of not having my own voice on the web and staying in my area of comfort in a relatively comfortable and stable job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
