<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</title>
    <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 20:18:21 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ramiroruiz.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Games IHG</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/games-ihg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 20:18:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/games-ihg/</guid>
      <description>I was contacted by the design agency V09 to help them create a new digital solution for their client. I also been helping IHG for different design projects for the last 5 years. I know them very well, I’ve been in their offices many times and that familiarity from both sides helped to have a smooth process.
V09 had some ideas but they were not sure if they were possible, they wanted a personalized game but the budget didn’t allow them to consider developing a native app/game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chromite Comercial</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/chromite-comercial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 02:08:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/chromite-comercial/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been helping Chromite for many years now since I was still in college, so I know the company quite well. At the beginning I help them with some editorial design, updating their product catalogs. I never liked their image but they were using it the same logo, fonts, and colors for all these years, they weren’t very keen to change all of it.
Years passed by and I kept working with them on other projects, one day while trying to fit my designs in their very outdated branding, I just had enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recicladora Industrial Mty</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/recicladora-industrial-mty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 02:27:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/recicladora-industrial-mty/</guid>
      <description>If you go and look for recycling businesses you get flooded with the ♻️ symbols, leaves and bright greenish colors. We wanted to move away from that, I went for other ways to differentiate and represent it. Taking references from the main focus of the company, tires, I took advantage of the name as is already very descriptive, so I opted for something subtle and abstract.
I came up with a round shape representing a tire, they’re similar figures around in a disorderly manner, symbolizing the pollution and waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra Servicios</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/extra-servicios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 02:30:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/work/extra-servicios/</guid>
      <description>Just starting the project I found interesting how different you can represent the two main services they offer. I wanted a rememberable mark for the company, is not easy to create an element that embodies cleaning and security at the same time. The other problem is they offer other small services for some of their clients, so the best was focus on the name as it already has a big meaning for his clients (Extra Services).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>