<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</title>
    <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learning on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 21:06:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ramiroruiz.com/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing my ways</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/changing-my-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 21:06:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/changing-my-ways/</guid>
      <description>A couple months ago, Frank Chimero, a great designer that I’d admired for a long time, wrote about the pain to re-learn many things in the web to keep yourself updated to the latest practices and trends. That post hit right on me as he expressed all my recent frustrations and everything I wanted to said but better.
First, let me start from the beginning. You see, I started learning about this web thing when I was in college studying graphic design and in all those years we end up having one little intro course of this newer area of design called “Web Design”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best resource to learn UI / UX</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/best-resource-to-learn-ui-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 09:18:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/best-resource-to-learn-ui-ux/</guid>
      <description>The best resource is understanding English.
Design is a discipline in constant evolution, the foundations and fundamentals will always be important but the implementation, channels, trends, and people change. So you have to be in constant movement and learning.
When you add that the design is aimed at the web or digital products, the speed of how things change increases exponentially. The source of most changes comes from the United States, thanks to its large market, its startups and global popularity, which is why the importance of English.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>