<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</title>
    <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Ramiro Ruiz, designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 22:32:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Fighting</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/back-to-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 22:32:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/back-to-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Last week, after almost 2 years without fighting. Past months full of problems, life-changing events, inactivity and a long recovery from an injury; I entered the cage again.
While I got to focus more on my design career and I even thought for a moment that it may be time to hang the gloves. As time pass I didn’t feel like myself and wasn’t happy with this version of me, I realize that a daily training regime and most importantly… High-level challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing my ways</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/changing-my-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 21:06:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/changing-my-ways/</guid>
      <description>A couple months ago, Frank Chimero, a great designer that I’d admired for a long time, wrote about the pain to re-learn many things in the web to keep yourself updated to the latest practices and trends. That post hit right on me as he expressed all my recent frustrations and everything I wanted to said but better.
First, let me start from the beginning. You see, I started learning about this web thing when I was in college studying graphic design and in all those years we end up having one little intro course of this newer area of design called “Web Design”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/new-website/</guid>
      <description>This morning I launched my new website. I used to be one of those designers that never reserved time for my brand, only working for clients and never on myself. As a result, I’ve never been really proud of my site.
I need to go back in history to my first portfolio site, that I superstitiously launch on September 9th, 2009 (09/09/09) looking for a bit of luck, raining clients or some kind of help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining Icalia Labs</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/joining-icalia-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 10:43:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/joining-icalia-labs/</guid>
      <description>I had a wild 2017, not exactly in a good way. Many sad events happened to my family in that year, thankfully our newborn helped us a lot. It gave us those moments of joy we needed.
During many months I lost focus in my training and work, but I needed to get back on my feet. So I started a new business inspired by the trend of productizing your services, aimed to create websites for small companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefit of Constraints</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/the-benefit-of-constraints/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 10:28:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/the-benefit-of-constraints/</guid>
      <description>When I was starting as a designer I regularly complain about restriction, feeling that I needed complete freedom to release my creativity.
I was young and didn’t fear the blank canvas, I would immediately start throwing and moving stuff around but all my results didn’t had any real authenticity and didn’t solve the problem effectively, just trendy designs all over the place, they represent what style I was inspired by in that moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best resource to learn UI / UX</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/best-resource-to-learn-ui-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 09:18:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/best-resource-to-learn-ui-ux/</guid>
      <description>The best resource is understanding English.
Design is a discipline in constant evolution, the foundations and fundamentals will always be important but the implementation, channels, trends, and people change. So you have to be in constant movement and learning.
When you add that the design is aimed at the web or digital products, the speed of how things change increases exponentially. The source of most changes comes from the United States, thanks to its large market, its startups and global popularity, which is why the importance of English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inherit fortune</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/inherit-fortune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 10:33:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/inherit-fortune/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago my father stayed in the hospital around 3 weeks, as in most places in the world, healthcare is very expensive, so he has social insurance which gives you medical care but it comes with a price. Hospitals are packed, few places to sit, little information and I don’t even want to talk about the restrooms.
You’ll see the mid to low income population in those places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play with fire and you get burned</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/play-with-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 09:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/play-with-fire/</guid>
      <description>On July 23, 2017, I experienced the worst accident I have ever had in my life.
It was a long-awaited weekend, where we went to Cuatrocienegas to have a great time with the family. Everything was excellent and wonderful, we finished going to the main places, the only place that was left before returning home was the marble mine, being there and having seen all I just had this urge to climb the highest stone (8-10 meters approx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resuming</title>
      <link>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/resuming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 08:20:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramiroruiz.com/blog/resuming/</guid>
      <description>On my birthday 5 years and 6 months ago on September 9, 2012, I wrote this:
 Hi there, well after so many years being part of the web passive community, today in my birthday I finally decided to make the change and start sharing the little I know and the many questions I ask myself constantly. Maybe I’m starting a bit late but I think I&amp;rsquo;ll take positive things from this instead of not doing it, besides I&amp;rsquo;m a little tired of being one more behind the monitor, of not having my own voice on the web and staying in my area of comfort in a relatively comfortable and stable job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>